export const easyLevel = [
    {
      question: "What does HTML stand for?",
      option1: "Hyperlinks and Text Markup Language",
      option2: "Hyper Text Markup Language",
      option3: "Home Tool Markup Language",
      option4: "Hyper Transfer Markup Language",
      ans: "Hyper Text Markup Language"
    },
    {
      question: "Which tag is used to define the largest heading in HTML?",
      option1: "<h6>",
      option2: "<heading>",
      option3: "<h1>",
      option4: "<head>",
      ans: "<h1>"
    },
    {
      question: "Which tag is used to create a hyperlink in HTML?",
      option1: "<link>",
      option2: "<a>",
      option3: "<href>",
      option4: "<hyperlink>",
      ans: "<a>"
    },
    {
      question: "Which HTML element is used to define a paragraph?",
      option1: "<p>",
      option2: "<para>",
      option3: "<paragraph>",
      option4: "<text>",
      ans: "<p>"
    },
    {
      question: "Which tag is used to display an image in HTML?",
      option1: "<picture>",
      option2: "<img>",
      option3: "<image>",
      option4: "<src>",
      ans: "<img>"
    },
    {
      question: "What is the correct HTML tag for inserting a line break?",
      option1: "<break>",
      option2: "<br>",
      option3: "<lb>",
      option4: "<line>",
      ans: "<br>"
    },
    {
      question: "Which tag is used to create an unordered list?",
      option1: "<ol>",
      option2: "<ul>",
      option3: "<list>",
      option4: "<li>",
      ans: "<ul>"
    },
    {
      question: "Which attribute is used to provide alternative text for an image?",
      option1: "alt",
      option2: "title",
      option3: "src",
      option4: "href",
      ans: "alt"
    },
    {
      question: "Which HTML tag is used to create a table?",
      option1: "<table>",
      option2: "<tab>",
      option3: "<tbl>",
      option4: "<t>",
      ans: "<table>"
    },
    {
      question: "Which tag is used to define a table row?",
      option1: "<row>",
      option2: "<tr>",
      option3: "<td>",
      option4: "<th>",
      ans: "<tr>"
    },
    {
      question: "Which HTML element is used to define the footer of a document?",
      option1: "<footer>",
      option2: "<bottom>",
      option3: "<end>",
      option4: "<foot>",
      ans: "<footer>"
    },
    {
      question: "Which tag is used to create a drop-down list?",
      option1: "<list>",
      option2: "<dropdown>",
      option3: "<select>",
      option4: "<option>",
      ans: "<select>"
    },
    {
      question: "Which HTML tag is used to define a division or section?",
      option1: "<section>",
      option2: "<div>",
      option3: "<span>",
      option4: "<article>",
      ans: "<div>"
    },
    {
      question: "Which tag is used to make text bold?",
      option1: "<bold>",
      option2: "<strong>",
      option3: "<b>",
      option4: "<text-bold>",
      ans: "<b>"
    },
    {
      question: "Which tag is used to create a numbered list?",
      option1: "<list>",
      option2: "<ol>",
      option3: "<ul>",
      option4: "<li>",
      ans: "<ol>"
    },
    {
      question: "What is the correct way to comment in HTML?",
      option1: "// This is a comment",
      option2: "/* This is a comment */",
      option3: "<!-- This is a comment -->",
      option4: "# This is a comment",
      ans: "<!-- This is a comment -->"
    },
    {
      question: "Which tag is used to create a form in HTML?",
      option1: "<input>",
      option2: "<form>",
      option3: "<button>",
      option4: "<fieldset>",
      ans: "<form>"
    },
    {
      question: "Which attribute is used to specify that an input field must be filled out?",
      option1: "validate",
      option2: "required",
      option3: "mandatory",
      option4: "fill",
      ans: "required"
    },
    {
      question: "Which tag is used to define a navigation section?",
      option1: "<nav>",
      option2: "<navigate>",
      option3: "<menu>",
      option4: "<section>",
      ans: "<nav>"
    },
    {
      question: "Which tag is used to play audio files in HTML?",
      option1: "<mp3>",
      option2: "<sound>",
      option3: "<audio>",
      option4: "<music>",
      ans: "<audio>"
    }
];

export const mediumLevel = [
    {
      question: "Which HTML tag is used to define a container for an external application or interactive content?",
      option1: "<embed>",
      option2: "<iframe>",
      option3: "<object>",
      option4: "<app>",
      ans: "<iframe>"
    },
    {
      question: "Which attribute is used to specify an image as a favicon for a webpage?",
      option1: "rel='favicon'",
      option2: "icon='favicon'",
      option3: "rel='icon'",
      option4: "type='favicon'",
      ans: "rel='icon'"
    },
    {
      question: "Which HTML5 tag is used to define self-contained content, like a blog post?",
      option1: "<section>",
      option2: "<article>",
      option3: "<aside>",
      option4: "<div>",
      ans: "<article>"
    },
    {
      question: "Which input type is used to select multiple options in a form?",
      option1: "checkbox",
      option2: "radio",
      option3: "text",
      option4: "select",
      ans: "checkbox"
    },
    {
      question: "Which attribute is used to open a hyperlink in a new tab?",
      option1: "new='tab'",
      option2: "target='_blank'",
      option3: "open='new'",
      option4: "href='new'",
      ans: "target='_blank'"
    },
    {
      question: "Which HTML5 tag is used to group related options in a drop-down list?",
      option1: "<option>",
      option2: "<select>",
      option3: "<datalist>",
      option4: "<optgroup>",
      ans: "<optgroup>"
    },
    {
      question: "Which attribute is used to set the background color of a table cell?",
      option1: "background-color",
      option2: "bgcolor",
      option3: "style",
      option4: "cellcolor",
      ans: "bgcolor"
    },
    {
      question: "Which tag is used to define a caption for a table?",
      option1: "<thead>",
      option2: "<title>",
      option3: "<caption>",
      option4: "<th>",
      ans: "<caption>"
    },
    {
      question: "Which HTML5 element is used to define important text?",
      option1: "<important>",
      option2: "<strong>",
      option3: "<em>",
      option4: "<b>",
      ans: "<strong>"
    },
    {
      question: "Which tag is used to specify a footer for a document or section?",
      option1: "<bottom>",
      option2: "<footer>",
      option3: "<end>",
      option4: "<div>",
      ans: "<footer>"
    },
    {
      question: "Which attribute is used to control how a video is loaded in HTML5?",
      option1: "load",
      option2: "autoplay",
      option3: "preload",
      option4: "buffer",
      ans: "preload"
    },
    {
      question: "Which tag is used to define an inline frame?",
      option1: "<frame>",
      option2: "<iframe>",
      option3: "<window>",
      option4: "<border>",
      ans: "<iframe>"
    },
    {
      question: "Which HTML5 tag is used to specify a key-pair for authentication?",
      option1: "<keygen>",
      option2: "<authenticate>",
      option3: "<passkey>",
      option4: "<security>",
      ans: "<keygen>"
    },
    {
      question: "Which element is used to group elements together for styling purposes?",
      option1: "<group>",
      option2: "<container>",
      option3: "<section>",
      option4: "<div>",
      ans: "<div>"
    },
    {
      question: "Which attribute is used to specify a default value for an input field?",
      option1: "value",
      option2: "default",
      option3: "placeholder",
      option4: "preset",
      ans: "value"
    },
    {
      question: "Which tag is used to display preformatted text?",
      option1: "<pre>",
      option2: "<code>",
      option3: "<text>",
      option4: "<format>",
      ans: "<pre>"
    },
    {
      question: "Which tag is used to add a JavaScript file to an HTML document?",
      option1: "<script>",
      option2: "<js>",
      option3: "<javascript>",
      option4: "<link>",
      ans: "<script>"
    },
    {
      question: "Which attribute is used to make an input field read-only?",
      option1: "disabled",
      option2: "readonly",
      option3: "locked",
      option4: "static",
      ans: "readonly"
    },
    {
      question: "Which tag is used to create a progress bar in HTML5?",
      option1: "<loading>",
      option2: "<progress>",
      option3: "<bar>",
      option4: "<meter>",
      ans: "<progress>"
    },
    {
      question: "Which tag is used to define a clickable button in HTML?",
      option1: "<input>",
      option2: "<click>",
      option3: "<button>",
      option4: "<submit>",
      ans: "<button>"
    }
];

export const hardLevel = [
    {
      question: "Which HTML tag is used to define a region in an image map?",
      option1: "<map>",
      option2: "<area>",
      option3: "<region>",
      option4: "<section>",
      ans: "<area>"
    },
    {
      question: "Which HTML5 attribute allows specifying multiple files for an input element?",
      option1: "multiple",
      option2: "multi",
      option3: "files",
      option4: "allow-multiple",
      ans: "multiple"
    },
    {
      question: "Which tag is used to provide a hint or a tooltip when hovering over an element?",
      option1: "title",
      option2: "tooltip",
      option3: "hint",
      option4: "alt",
      ans: "title"
    },
    {
      question: "Which HTML element is used to define an interactive user interface component, such as a toggle switch?",
      option1: "<ui>",
      option2: "<interactive>",
      option3: "<details>",
      option4: "<dialog>",
      ans: "<details>"
    },
    {
      question: "Which attribute is used to specify a media query for a <link> element?",
      option1: "query",
      option2: "media",
      option3: "condition",
      option4: "match",
      ans: "media"
    },
    {
      question: "Which HTML element is used to define the relationship between a document and an external resource?",
      option1: "<link>",
      option2: "<a>",
      option3: "<meta>",
      option4: "<rel>",
      ans: "<link>"
    },
    {
      question: "Which HTML5 tag is used to define a scalar measurement within a known range?",
      option1: "<progress>",
      option2: "<meter>",
      option3: "<range>",
      option4: "<scale>",
      ans: "<meter>"
    },
    {
      question: "Which HTML attribute specifies that a script should be executed after the page has been parsed?",
      option1: "defer",
      option2: "async",
      option3: "delay",
      option4: "wait",
      ans: "defer"
    },
    {
      question: "Which HTML element is used to define the possible options for an input field?",
      option1: "<options>",
      option2: "<datalist>",
      option3: "<select>",
      option4: "<list>",
      ans: "<datalist>"
    },
    {
      question: "Which HTML tag is used to define keyboard input?",
      option1: "<kbd>",
      option2: "<key>",
      option3: "<input>",
      option4: "<code>",
      ans: "<kbd>"
    },
    {
      question: "Which tag is used to specify text that should be isolated from its surrounding text for formatting?",
      option1: "<iso>",
      option2: "<bdi>",
      option3: "<i>",
      option4: "<strong>",
      ans: "<bdi>"
    },
    {
      question: "Which HTML element is used to specify an external source for a media element like <video> or <audio>?",
      option1: "<src>",
      option2: "<source>",
      option3: "<media>",
      option4: "<external>",
      ans: "<source>"
    },
    {
      question: "Which tag is used to define side content that is indirectly related to the main content?",
      option1: "<sidebar>",
      option2: "<aside>",
      option3: "<div>",
      option4: "<section>",
      ans: "<aside>"
    },
    {
      question: "Which attribute specifies that an input field must be filled out before submitting a form?",
      option1: "required",
      option2: "validate",
      option3: "mandatory",
      option4: "fill",
      ans: "required"
    },
    {
      question: "Which HTML element is used to display contact information for the author or owner of a document?",
      option1: "<info>",
      option2: "<author>",
      option3: "<address>",
      option4: "<contact>",
      ans: "<address>"
    }
];

export const html = [easyLevel, mediumLevel, hardLevel];